War is a Bitch
The Devil's Rock is a fantasy, horror, thriller film directed by Paul Campion.
Set in the Channel Islands on the eve of D Day, two Kiwi commandos, sent to destroy German gun emplacements to distract
Hitler's forces away from Normandy, discover a Nazi occult plot to unleash demonic forces to win the war.
Captain Ben Grogan, played by Craig Hall.
Col Klaus Meyer, played by Matthew Sunderland.
Helena, played by Gina Varela.
Sergeant Joe Tane, played by Karlos Drinkwater.
Nicole, played by Jessica Grace Smith.
Private Muller, played by Luke Hawker.
The Devil's Rock is a 2011 New Zealand horror film produced by Leanne Saunders, directed by Paul Campion, written by Campion,
Paul Finch, and Brett Ihaka, and starring Craig Hall, Matthew Sunderland, Gina Varela, and Karlos Drinkwater.
It is set in the Channel Islands on the eve of D-Day and tells the story of two New Zealand
commandos who discover a Nazi occult plot to unleash a demon to win World War II.
The film combines elements of war films and supernatural horror films.
The film was theatrically released on 8 July 2011 in the United
Kingdom and 22 September 2011 in New Zealand.
The film explores themes of nazi, new zealand, black magic, occult, succubus.
The tone is dark and intense.